Now that I have inserted the text into
the presentation, it's time to think
about the actual formatting available.
At the moment, the presentation
contains four slides with a plain
white background and some text.
What I need to do I'm going to try
and enhance the document, and the
first thing I'm going to do is insert
some images on the first slide.
So if I select insert and
there's a variety of tools along
here, but I'm going to focus on
inserting a couple of pictures.
So if I select a picture icon
and the first picture I'm going
to insert is from this device.
So I've already got that
saved on my computer.
So I select that and then it'll take me
to the location where I've saved image,
and then double click on it and that
inserts that into the presentation.
As you can see, there are a number of
icons around the edge of the image.
If I click and hold on those,
they allow me to resize the image.
I can also rotate the image accordingly.
If you wish to maintain the aspect ratio,
you should ensure that you use the corner
buttons to change the size of the picture.
So now I have inserted the first picture
I'm going to look for another one.
And if I click on insert again,
select picture and this time I'm
going to go for a stock image.
So I look for a stock image and I'm
going to do a search for "balloon",
and that will bring up a range
of images relating to balloon.
And I will just select that one that
will insert that into the slide.
As you can see, it's very large.
So again I need to resize
that and reduce the size down.
So I use the corner tab to
do that and place it there.
And rotate it a little bit.
I'm just going to make it
a little bit bigger again.
So it's more consistent
with the other image.
Okay.
So now I have the two images
in, I can apply a range of
formatting to the actual images.
So if I click and select an image and
then go to the picture styles and move
my mouse over the various icons, it
will make changes to the actual image.
And you can expand that and there
are other options available.
Again, I can then also crop an image.
If I select an image and select the crop
tool, you will see some black bounding
markers come around the edge of the image.
So if I move those in and then
click away, it will reduce the size.
I'll just undo that by Control and  Z.
So as you can see if I wanted to reduce
the size of that image, so that one's
more square, this one's more rectangular.
So I click on the image, select the
crop tool and move it in from the side.
So it's more square click away that will
automatically do that and I can resize it.
So it is more in keeping with
the image on the left-hand side.
So they're more or less the same size now.
As well as that you can actually
group your items together.
So if I want to make sure that
whatever formatting I apply to
that image is also applied to that
one, I can link them together.
So if I click on that image and then
hold down the control key and click
on that image, I can now go to the
group objects icon and select group.
So that has now grouped those together.
So as you see, if I go now to the picture
styles bar and start moving along the
icons and we'll change them to whichever
icon I select and it changes both images.
So I'll select that one there.
So both images are now linked.
So whatever apply to one will
automatically be applied to the other.
Again, if you wish to ungroup them,
you would just simply go to - make sure
they're highlighted, or the box that
is surrounding them is highlighted.
Go to that, go to ungroup.
And then that means that they
are now individual again.
One other feature that I'd like
to demonstrate here is how you can
actually place an image behind text.
So at the moment, I've inserted
the images into the presentation.
If I click on the image
and move it around, it will
automatically cover the text.
So I just leave that there.
And again, I'll do that with that one.
So at the moment, they are now covering
the text, but if I right click on
the image, I can then send to back.
So if I send it backwards.
And again, for that one send to back, it
automatically allows the text to be shown.
And the images and a background,
it may not look nice aesthetically
but it's something that you can do.
I could increase the size of that.
And again, the size of that.
As you can see, it would
still have the text.
So I could change the, highlight
the text and change the color
to make it more emphasized and
again, with the sales report.
So those are various features and
tools just to enhance the document.
And as you can see this, the style
that has been applied to the images,
also giving it a shadow image.